I just saw Kathy naked.
It was like torture.
If we go to war and you're captured,
you're in for a surprise.
It keeps getting worse.
It bad enough that I'm in love
with my roommate's girlfriend.
Every time we're in the same room,
there's weird energy between us.
Call me crazy, but
I think she likes me too.
And now I have seen her naked.
At least with her clothes on...
...I could imagine her body
was covered in boils.
But there are no boils.
She's smooth.
Smooth!
-Could everyone see up his robe?
-Oh, my God!
The One Where
Chandler Crosses the Line
-Here you go.
-I'll call you.
Great!
Hey, hey. Who was that?
Casey. We're going out tonight.
Going out? Wow!
It didn't work out
with Kathy? Bummer.
No, things are fine.
I'm having a late meal with her
after an early one with Casey.
-What?
-Yeah.
The craziest thing is,
I just ate a whole pizza myself.
You're going out with Kathy!
Yeah. Why are you upset?
Well, I'm upset...
...for you.
Sex with an endless line of beautiful
women must be unfulfilling.
What's the big deal?
It's not like we're exclusive.
Look, Joey.
Kathy's clearly not fulfilling
your emotional needs.
But, Casey....
Granted, I just saw
the back of her head.
But I got this sense
that she's smart and funny...
...and gets you.
You got all that
from the back of her head?
I think it's time
for you to settle down.
Make a choice.
Pick a lane.
Who's Elaine?
Little Tony Tarzan
Swinging on a nose hair
Swinging with the greatest of ease
I don't know the next verse.
You could just go:
Greatest of ease
Then go right into it.
I like that.
How do you know about...?
You know, I used to play.
That's right.
The keyboards?
A little in high school.
I got into it in college.
That's when
I really found my sound.
Orange juice just came out
of my nose, but it was worth it.
Oh, my God!
I completely forgot about
your sound.
He'd lock himself in
the basement for hours.
No one was ever allowed to hear
the sound.
I want to hear the sound.
No, I mean,
I haven't played in so long.
Well, it's really personal stuff.
Play that funky music, white boy.
-Yeah, come on.
-No, you guys.
My keyboards are all the way
Yeah, okay.
Who wants to get dinner later?
I wanna try that new ltalian restaurant.
Supposed to be really good. Saw a
lot of Chinese people eating in there.
What are you talking about?
You said some restaurant must be good
because Chinese people were eating there.
That's because it was
a Chinese restaurant.
I still wanna go.
Who wants to come?
Oh, I can't. I got two dinner dates
tonight, so I gotta get ready.
All right, girls' night out.
Sorry, but we have to prep that
catering thing for tomorrow.
Oh, that's right.
I wish I could eat
in restaurants alone.
You should try it.
It's a really good thing to do.
I just think I'd feel really self-conscious.
Like I was on display or something.
I was on display once.
Nothing like eating alone.
I just had a great time with myself.
Well, this could be a good story.
At dinner.
It was so liberating.
You know, I don't need people to
have fun. I'm fun. I'm a fun girl.
Are you a naughty girl?
No, just fun. Fun. Good. Fun.
-See, I told you you'd have fun.
-I know.
Although I must say that I totally
judge any woman I see eating alone.
-Why?
-What's wrong with a woman eating alone?
Well, obviously something.
She's eating alone.
Okay, guys.
All right! Bring it on, you!
Here we go.
You know, I've never played
my stuff for anyone before.
So it's important that
you understand...
...it's about communicating...
...very private emotions.
You know....
You should think of my work...
...as wordless sound poems.
-That's what
-Oh, my God, play.
Well, you know, that was...
...terrific!
Really...
...bitchen.
Wow! It was so wow!
Really?
Yeah! I mean, you should
play in public.
Wow, thanks, you guys.
That's
I want to play you another piece.
I left my helicopter sounds on
another disk. I'll be right back, okay?
This is so nice.
I mean, I am so....
God bless my dad for
soundproofing the basement.
I can't believe I ever let him
touch me with those fingers.
What are you guys talking about?
I loved it!
It was so moving.
It's so different
from the stuff you usually hear.
You mean, music?
I know what you think.
Yes, yes, your breasts
are just as firm and juicy.
Come in.
Oh, God! Is that Baywatch?
Yes, but I just watch it
for the articles.
-So is Joey around?
-No, he's not back yet.
Come in, have a seat.
Bow or stern?
I don't have a preference. You?
I like it in the stern.
Of the boat.
It's me. Casey and l
had a little car trouble.
-What happened?
-We broke down.
I have to get transmission fluid.
Tell Kathy that I'm sorry
and I'll be there soon.
-Why can't you tell her?
-I think my time is about to
I thought your time ran out.
Me too, but I guess I do have
Joey's running a little late,
and he says he's sorry.
I guess it's just you and me, then.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I think it is.
So, what'd you do today?
I had an appointment
to cut my hair.
-Looks great!
-And then it got canceled.
-I could cut it.
-Really? Do you do that?
Yeah, I learned at my aunt's
dog-grooming shop. What do you say?
Dog grooming?
Don't make my tail too poofy.
You have really great hair.
Oh, thanks. I grow it myself.
You know who also
has great hair is Joey.
Yes, Joey has great hair.
I'm basically done here.
Let me get this hair off your neck.
What are you doing?
Checking to see if it's even.
Looks good.
The phone!
The phone's making sounds!
Hey, dude, it's me.
Hey, it's Joey!
It looks like we'll be stuck here.
I got the fluid.
The transmission wasn't there.
-What?
-It fell out.
I just figured we hit a dog.
Could you put Kathy on?
I want to apologize to her.
It's Joey.
No, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, no, stop apologizing.
It's okay.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
I should probably go.
I forgot my purse.
I really did.
-This is bad! It's bad!
-Horrible!
Wait, the kiss or the situation?
The kiss was good.
-But that's bad!
-Here's what we do.
-We forget it happened.
-What?
We swallow our feelings, even if
we're unhappy forever. Sound good?
Can you really do that?
I have to. He's my best friend.
And you're seeing him.
Chandler, I like Joey a lot.
-But with you
-No, don't! Don't, see?
You're getting me confused.
I'm starting to yearn.
I'm sorry.
If you want to pretend that
nothing happened, I can try.
I think we have to.
Are you still out there?
Electrifying
Infinite time
There's a Starbucks
about three blocks down.
He's so inspired.
Just look at him. Look at him go!
Thank you very much!
Hey, aren't you up next?
-I'm not playing tonight.
-Why not?
I can't follow Ross.
It'd be like those
poor bicycle-riding chimps...
...who had to
follow the Beatles. No.
Ross sucks.
The place has emptied because of him.
Oh, my God, he's not even
appreciated in his own time.
I'd give anything to not be
appreciated in my own time!
You suck too.
You're awful.
You guys!
You suck too!
Man! I can't believe
I locked myself out again!
Hang on, buddy.
Oh, my God! What happened?
-Did you do all this? Why?
-I sure did.
It made me feel good to do
something nice for my friend.
You're amazing.
No, this is amazing.
A TV that appears
as if from nowhere!
That's the dream!
How did you afford all this?
I'm 29. I mean, who needs
a savings account?
You're the best friend
anyone has ever had.
I don't know.
No, you are.
You do this, you give me advice....
What you said about
focusing on one woman?
I'll do that.
With Casey?
I'll see how things go with Kathy.
She's cool.
-Or Casey.
-No, Kathy.
-Could be Casey.
Consider Casey.
I think somebody's
got a little crush on Casey.
I'll fix you two up.
What do you think?
That all the pieces of my life
are falling right into place.
You were really great.
You were really, really great.
Thanks.
Monica tells me you don't want
to play anymore because of me...
...and, you know, my talent.
Is that true?
Well, kind of, yeah.
I was trying to be really okay
and upbeat about it...
...but I just feel so dwarfed
by your musical gift.
See, but....
Pheebs, that is the exact
opposite intent of my music.
You know, my music
is meant to inspire.
If it bothers you this much...
...then I won't play anymore.
No, don't do that.
How could I live if I knew I was
depriving the world of your music?
Yeah, okay.
-I'd love to, but I have plans on Sunday.
-Well, maybe some other time.
-Sure. Just give me a call, I'm in the book.
-Okay. Thanks a lot. See you.
What are you doing?
He is cute, and he's a doctor.
-How do you know?
-Honey, I eavesdrop because I care.
-Well, I have plans on Sunday.
-With who?
-Me.
-Oh, God.
You are the one who told me how
important it is to spend time alone.
I can't just go out with that guy
when I have plans with myself.
Wouldn't be fair to me.
So basically you're saying you
don't want to cheat on yourself.
Well, if you wanna make
me sound crazy.
Saw the new furniture. Very nice.
Joey has the best boyfriend ever!
I kissed Kathy.
Are you serious?
-Does Joey know?
-No.
Is there any way you think
he will understand this?
You obviously haven't
screwed over your friends.
Which we all appreciate.
If you'd told him how you felt
before you kissed her...
...knowing Joey,
he'd have stepped aside.
Don't say that!
That's not true, is it?
Yeah, he loves you.
Then why didn't you
tell me to do that?
I said something to Phoebe.
And I thought it was
a really good idea.
-Yeah, I remember.
-Oh, my God!
What am I going to do?
-You'll have to tell him.
-Why do I have to tell him?
-Because you do.
-Yeah, I know.
Would it be okay
if I wrote a song about this?
I don't know if this is
working out. I think....
I think I wanna see other people.
Wow. Didn't see that coming.
It's not that I don't
enjoy this. I do.
I just wanna see
what else is out there.
Hey, Guy. What are you doing here?
I work across the street.
-lt turns out I'm gonna be free Sunday.
-I wish you had called me.
I just told them I'd work this weekend.
Okay, well, maybe next weekend.
-Definitely. I'll see you.
-Okay.
Yeah, you'll be talking to me never,
because you're a freak who eats alone.
Sambuca margarita?
It that a real thing?
Well, we only had sambuca,
so it is now.
Listen, Joe. I need to I need
to talk to you about something.
What's up?
It's about Kathy.
I like her.
I like her a lot, actually.
-You do?
-Yeah.
Your timing couldn't be better.
She's not my girlfriend anymore.
What?
-Yeah, she broke up with me.
-When?
Just now, after acting class.
I thought she was doing some scene,
so I let people watch.
Man, I am so sorry.
Are you okay?
I've been better, but I'm all right.
So you like her?
Yes, but I don't have to.
No, it's okay.
You know why?
Because you came to me first.
I thought that would be
the best thing to do.
You might have your work
cut out for you.
When I talked to her, I got
the feeling she's into some other guy.
See, that's actually what
I wanted to talk to you about.
I think I know who the other guy is.
Who?
It's me.
I'm the other guy.
What?
When you were late last night,
Kathy and I got to talking...
...and one thing led
to another, and....
And what?
Did you sleep with her?
-No, I just kissed her.
-What? That's even worse!
-How is that worse?
-It's the same!
There's nothing I could do.
I think I'm in love with her!
Who cares?
You went behind my back?
I'd never do that to you!
I have no excuses.
I was totally over the line.
You're so far past the line,
that you can't even see the line!
The line is a dot to you!
Yes, right! And I feel horrible.
You have to believe me.
Oh, my God. Is that
why you bought all this stuff?
You know what?
I will not watch your TV.
I won't listen to your stereo.
And there's a loaf in the new
bread maker I won't eat. Know why?
-Probably because
-It's all tainted with your betrayal!
This apartment is empty to me!
I'm not happy about you either.
And just so you know...
...I made that bread for you.
Oh, my God! He's lost it.
He's totally lost it.
What?
This cannot get any worse.
Rats in the basement
are hanging themselves.
Thank you. Thanks.
I lost it.
I won't play anymore.
Would you?
Can you finish my set?
After that? Yeah.
No, I mean, if I can help.
Yeah, like I could lose it.
What?
I played bad on purpose, guys.
Okay, you were trying to
play bad this whole time.
No. Just that last song.